

LEADERSHIP STYLE

MIX OF AUTOCRATIC AND
PARTICIPATIVE; STRIVE FOR
PERFECTION IN EVERYTHING
AND SET AMBITIOUS GOALS FOR
SELF AND OTHERS

SKILLS

MICROSOFT OFFICE

TIME MANAGEMENT

LEADERSHIP

PROBLEM-SOLVING

ORGANIZATION

CRITICAL THINKING

DATA ANALYSIS

ADAPTABILITY

POSITIVITY

BUCKET LIST

TRAVEL TO EVERY CONTINENT

BECOME FLUENT IN SPANISH

OBTAIN MY MBA

BUY A HOUSE

GET MARRIED

DESIGN A WEBPAGE

TRAVEL TO ALL 50 STATES

Go Skydiving

CLIMB A MOUNTAIN

Make a difference

Amber Gestreich

2330 LEXINGTON AVE SOUTH, APT 218
MENDOTA HEIGHTS, MN 55120
UNITED STATES OF AMERICA

AMBER.M.OESTREICH@GMAIL.COM • +1 651-231-5721 WWW.AMBEROESTREICH.COM

SUMMARY:

Experienced IKEA co-worker with a strong background in leadership and logistics. Obtained Bachelor's in International Business in May of 2019 and currently working towards Master of Business Administration in a Management concentration with expected graduation in December 2021.

EDUCATION:



ST CATHERINE UNIVERSITY

Master of Business Administration, Management September 2019 to Present (Expected December 2021)



University of Minnesota—Crookston

Bachelor of Science, International Business August 2012 to May 2019

Experience:



IKEA—BLOOMINGTON, MN

Preparation & Flow Team Lead (October 2019 to Present)

- Assist in the development of co-workers and peers
- Create schedules to optimize the use of available hours
- Ensure all federal, state, and company regulations are adhered to
- Plan and implement product placement within the warehouse
- Monitor and evaluate assigned space capacities to ensure available stock

Preparation & Flow Co-Worker (August 2017 to October 2019)

- Operate machinery to company and OSHA standards
- Fulfill customer orders
- Plan and implement product locations within warehouse
- Ensure daily load-out is efficiently completed while solving problems that
- Complete aisle maintenance throughout each shift

Self Service Co-Worker (April 2016 to August 2017)

- Prepare space in warehouse for overnight replenishment
- Assist in planning warehouse space for new products
- Assist customers with their shopping needs